dksh.com 2019-08-20

# Privacy

**Privacy Statement**  
DKSH respects your privacy and is committed to comply with applicable data protection laws and to safeguard your personal data. This Privacy Statement describes the way in which we, DKSH Management Ltd. and its Group companies (DKSH) collect, use and share personal data about you, how we safeguard your personal data and interact with third parties that may have access to your personal data and finally, how you can contact us in case of questions or requests. 

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal data as described in this Privacy Statement. You also acknowledge that DKSH may periodically change, update or remove this Privacy Statement at its discretion. In this case, we will post updated versions of this Privacy Statement on this page. A revised Privacy Statement will apply only to data collected subsequent to its effective date. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of our services following the positing of changes to the Privacy Statement will mean you accept those changes. 

This Privacy Statement applies to personal data collected by DKSH online, such as through this website, email and other online tools and applications, but not to offline collection.

**Personal data we collect about you**  
As part of your interactions with us, we may collect personal data about you as far as it is necessary to conduct our legitimate business interests, to comply with a legal obligation or as agreed by you. 

Most of our services do not require any form of registration, allowing you to visit our website without providing us with any information about you. However, some services may require you to register and therefore to provide us with your personal data. The types of personal data we collect depend on the interactions you have with us and the services you use, they may include your title, first name, last name, company, department, email address, phone, street, building number, zip code, city and country. 

We may also collect your personal data by tracking how you interact with our website, for example by using cookies. We may collect the Internet Protocol (IP) address, a number assigned to your computer whenever you access our website to conduct system administration and report aggregated information to affiliates, business partners and/or vendors who conduct website analysis and website performance reviews on our behalf. We may further collect your utilization data, e.g. information on the beginning, end and extent of each access, and information on the telecommunications services you accessed. In some instances, we may ask for your consent for collecting and using your personal data for the purposes as outlined in this Privacy Statement, in particular for sending you marketing materials, such as explanatory brochures and information or newsletters or when you participate in any online survey. 

**How we use your personal data**  
We will only collect and use personal data about you as described in this Privacy Statement and as necessary 

  * to provide you with our services and to process your order 
  * to respond to your requests 
  * to manage our customer relationship with you
  * to send you relevant marketing materials
  * to invite you to register for an event
  * to invite you to participate in an online survey
  * to provide you with our media and investor relations information
  * to prevent fraud or other illegal activities, such as willful attacks to DKSH information technology systems
  * to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense or to support any legal or criminal investigation
  * and otherwise to the extent as permitted or required by applicable laws

We may further anonymize and aggregate data collected through this website for statistical purposes to help us improve our products and services. Subject to your specific permission that we may collect separately and to your full control to opt out at any time, we may also use your personal data to send you promotional material or newsletters that we think may be of interest to you.

**Cookies and usage tracking**  
We use cookies, small text files that are automatically placed on your computer’s hard drive when you access certain websites and similar technologies, directly or through third parties, such as web analytics services like Google Analytics. Cookies allow us to store information, such as your domain name, your internet service provider, your operating system, the date and time of access, the pages you visit or the types of searches you perform. 

We may use this information to store your preferences and settings, help improve the contents of our website, to enable you to register to websites and applications, to compile aggregated statistics to evaluate visitors’ use of our website or website activity and for internal and market research purposes.  

You have the right to choose whether or not to accept cookies and to opt out of Google Analytics. You can block cookies by changing your browser settings so that cookies from the website cannot be placed on your computer or mobile device. However, please note that if you choose to refuse cookies, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the website. For further information about our use of cookies, please see below our Cookie Policy. For more information about Google Analytics, or how to opt out of Google Analytics, please [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

**Links to other websites**  
DKSH websites contain links to other websites. Please note that any of these sites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices or the content of other websites but only for the websites controlled by DKSH. 

**Who we share your personal data with**  
We may share, or otherwise disclose your personal data to our affiliated companies or other trusted business partners providing services on our behalf, such as for technical support, to evaluate the usefulness of this website, for marketing purposes or for other types of service delivery. We have contracts in place with these parties to ensure that personal data is processed based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Statement and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We only share your personal data with the parties mentioned above and other third parties, including governmental authorities, as far as this is necessary to provide any services that you have requested or authorized by accepting the terms of this Privacy Statement, to protect your, our, or others’ rights, property or safety, to maintain the security of our services or if we are required to share your personal data to comply with applicable laws, court or other governmental regulations, or if such disclosure is otherwise necessary in support of any legal or criminal investigation or legal proceeding. 

Please note that DKSH companies and subsidiaries, as well as authorities, customers and suppliers to whom we may disclose your personal data, may be located outside your country of domicile, including countries in Asia and potentially the United States of America, whose data protection laws may differ from those in the country in which you are located. In such cases, we will ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place to protect your personal data by implementing appropriate legal mechanisms, such as EU Standard Contractual Clauses. For more information about the safeguards we take, please send us an email via a form here: Online Communications

**How we secure your personal data**  
DKSH has implemented technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access to personal data we store. This includes training of our personnel who may have access to your personal data.

**How long we store your personal data**  
We will store your personal data as long as required to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement, unless a longer or shorter retention period is required or permitted by law. 

**Your rights in respect to your personal data**  
You have the right to request to be notified about what personal data we hold from you and to request the correction or deletion of your personal data that is held by us or by a third party with whom we conduct business. In addition, where the processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please be aware that the withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on your consent before its withdrawal. Under certain circumstances, you have further the right to object to or to request the restriction of the processing of your personal data and, if you reside in the EU, you may lodge a complaint to your data protection authority if you consider that the processing of your personal data infringes applicable laws. 

If you would like to make such request, please contact us as described in the section “How to contact us” below. After providing proof of identity, we will respond within a reasonable time.

**Cookie Policy  **       

**What is a cookie?**  
Cookies are small files which are stored on your computer to keep track of your visit to the website and your preferences; as you move between pages, and sometimes to save settings between visits. Cookies help the builders of websites gather statistics about how often people visit certain areas of the site and help in tailoring websites to be more useful and user-friendly.

**The types of cookies we use**  
_Session cookies_  
Not used by DKSH. 

_Persistent cookies_  
Persistent cookies remain on your device for a longer period and are used by our website to recognize your device when you return. 

**How to control and deactivate cookies**  
Most browsers are set so that they automatically accept cookies. You may however, deactivate the storage of cookies or set your browser in a manner that it will notify you as soon as cookies are set.  
Alternatively, you can visit <https://ico.org.uk/global/cookies/>, which contains information on how to deactivate cookies on a variety of desktop browsers. 

**How to contact us**  
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Statement, or want to request access to your personal data or exercise your privacy rights, please contact us:

DKSH Management Ltd.    
Wiesenstrasse 8  
8008 Zürich  
Switzerland

Online Communications

This Privacy Statement is effective as of May 25, 2018.
